Where have you been?
Hunting and gathering.
Ah. The victim's name
is Timothy Hartley.
He was killed sometime last night.
He was shot in the chest, and then
his throat was slit. Charming.
His I.D. says he's from
about a hundred miles away
from here... Hillsborough.
No sign of what he was doing up here.
Sheriff says Hartley's
car's down the road.
I'll check it out. All right.
You tell him? Tell him what?
Coroner's office sent Steiner.
Dr. Steiner?
And we all know how much you
like to make fun of Dr. Steiner,
So don't, okay?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
No humoring yourself at his expense.
Is he that way?
Top of the morning to you, Steiner.
You're looking trim.
Jane.
Curiously considerate killer.
Slit his throat after the shots
to put him out of his misery.
Three steps back, please.
What?
Please maintain a distance
Of at least three steps
from the body. Why?
Because this body is a no-Jane zone.
It will not be a playground for you.
You will not touch it or sniff
it or place playing cards on it
Or borrow it for an interrogation.
If you do, a deputy will remove you.
Clear?
That's a little harsh, no?
You have driven me to
desperate measures.
Well, I'm nothing
if I'm not respectful
Of my fellow crime-fighters.
But I can see everything I
need to from here anyway.
Really? W...
What exactly do you see?
He's in money, but not a banker,
Something more aggressive...
stocks or such, social drinker,
Increased his intake lately,
So under some pressure.
A registered, uh, independent,
though always votes republican,
And as much money as he
has, his wife has more.
Ridiculous. He chose the
tasteless tasseled loafers.
She bought the opal-enlaced
sterling silver cuff links.
Guesses.
You might as well say he's going
to meet a tall, dark stranger.
That's very unlikely, doctor.
He's dead.
And by the way, it looks
like there's something
In his left-front pant pocket.
You are about to think,
"What the hell"? "How did Jane..."
"Do that?"
How did you do that?
"There are more things in
heaven and earth, Horatio,
"Than dreamt of in your philosophy."
Okay. You planned ahead.
You asked one of the sheriff's
deputies to call you
The next time Steiner was on a case
And then you asked
them to plant the note.
That is an absurd theory.
You know this means another
apology at the coroner's office.
No, it doesn't.
Steiner loves the attention. Lisbon.
What happened?
Where are they?
Robbery. Two guys in a pickup
pulled the coroner's van over
And held it up. What'd they steal?
Huh. Get this... your vic's body.
Hartley's corpse?
That's right.
Steiner tried to stop them,
believe it or not.
Dr. Steiner.
Agent Lisbon.
It's not as bad as it looks.
Go get yourself checked out
and then come talk to us.
Jane, was this you?
W... another trick?
Oh. Jane had nothing to do
with this, nothing at all.
You didn't, did you?
Of course not.
Swear on your life?
On your life, even.
Damn it. Who steals a body?
Interesting.
Sync by YYeTs
Corrected by ThreeSixes
www.addic7ed.com
The pickup was... pulled over.
There were two men, apparently
working on the engine.
They flagged us down,
For help, we thought, and
then they pulled out guns.
Can you describe them?
They were both white,
A little under 6 feet, I think.
I can't really say much more.
They wore hooded s...
jackets and sunglasses.
One went to the van and
dragged the body bag out.
The one guarding us went
to help him, and...
That's when I...
Intervened.
Foolish.
For once, I agree with you. Mnh.
They put the body into the
truck and they... they took off.
Why would anyone do this?
We don't know yet. It's early.
I have to take this. I'm sorry.
Thank you for your time, Dr. Steiner.
Of course.
Good-bye again, mr. Jane.
It wasn't your fault.
Excuse me?
They had guns.
Big, scary guns.
There's nothing you could do.
The body is my responsibility,
my reason for being here.
Now I have no reason
or responsibility.
There's nothing for me to do.
I don't expect you to understand
Why that feels like failure to me,
but it does.
Want a cup of tea?
I don't think so.
Suit yourself.
I like the chapel in Yountville.
It's just a long way
for the guests to go.
What did you find out about
Vandermeer State Park?
I love that place.
I see.
Well, I guess we'll just keep looking.
I love you. Bye.
Vandermeer State Park...
Beautiful for a wedding.
I've hiked there.
There's an old quaker meeting house.
Oh, it would be perfect,
But I guess they don't allow weddings.
It's too hard on the
ground vegetation.
What do we have on Hartley?
Jane was right.
He was in finance.
Ran a hedge fund called
the H.V. Wilder Fund.
But his wife's family has the real money.
Name's Cook. The Cooks?
Yeah, I guess.
Wife's name is Peregrine.
I'll deal with the family.
You go and talk to the
people he worked with.
Anything on the missing corpse?
Forensics found no
usable prints on the van
And nothing from the tire
tracks at the scene.
Why steal a dead body?
What can they use it for?
Got me.
Go and have another talk with the
two guys that were with Steiner.
Get any details on the
thieves or the truck.
Van Pelt, look for
any similar crimes,
Bodies that were
stolen from hospitals,
ambulances, anything.
Good luck with the Cooks.
Yeah, nothing like telling people
Their loved ones are dead,
And oh, by the way,
we lost the corpse.
None of this makes any sense.
The last time I-I spoke to Tim,
He was telling me some stupid
joke he heard at work,
Happy as can be.
Who's responsible, agent?
My son-in-law didn't just disappear.
Someone is accountable.
Who?
Ma'am, we don't know yet.
We're doing the best we can.
Not good enough.
Mother!
My dear, when they tell you
they're doing their very best,
That's exactly what they aren't doing.
Hell of a place you've got here.
Where'd you get the money for it?
Excuse me?
The moolah. The scratch.
The shekels. The dollarinis.
What does that have
to do with anything?
Obviously something
you're embarrassed about.
Sugar beets. Sugar beets?
My, uh, my grandfather grew them.
I love sugar beets.
There's no shame in
sugar beets, Elspeth.
Mrs. Hartley, we found
your husband's body
A hundred miles from here.
Any idea what he was doing out there?
Uh, no, none at all.
Was there anything out of the ordinary
going on in his life?
Troubles at work?
Changes in his schedule?
No. We started...
Talking about having...
A family...
A while back.
There, there, dear.
If there are no more questions...
You didn't like your
son-in-law, did you?
You found him vulgar despite
his highfalutin job.
And you... you're frightened.
The body's disappearance alarms
you in a very specific way.
What is that?
Harrison, please show
our visitors out.
Thank you. I'm good.
Oh, God.
Why do these things happen?
How long have you and Mr.
Hartley been partners?
Oh, uh, five years or so.
We were both interested in a fund
That offered slightly esoteric
financial instruments.
A hedge fund.
What we do is pretty complicated.
I don't want to bore
you with the details.
As I understand it,
you rely on a strategy
That exploits mean
reversion tendencies
Of crosscurrent far forward rates.
Is that right? Yes.
What did Mr. Hartley
do for the fund?
Built it.
Designed the strategy.
Certifiable genius.
The best.
A fund like yours can lose
people a lot of money.
Any angry investors? No, no, no.
Recently, we've had excellent returns.
What about work?
Did hartley have problems here?
"Loved" Is the word.
How about trouble at home?
No. Tim adored Peregrine.
He... he... he was a boy scout.
He would never play around,
wouldn't even think of it.
He's a straight... straight arrow.
I see.
The straightest.
So nothing new from
the guys with Steiner,
But it wasn't an entirely
wasted journey. I got scones.
I found something.
Three other corpses have been stolen
From vehicles leaving crime scenes
over the past six months.
Huh. Who caught the cases?
We did. Rigsby. O'Laughlin.
Why is the FBI on this?
It's interstate. One of the
corpses was taken in Nevada.
You guys have a theory? Yeah.
We think the bodies are
being sold at tissue banks.
Tissue banks? They harvest bone
and tissue from the corpses,
Then sell them to
medical supply houses.
You're supposed to get
permission from the family
To sell the corpse, but these
guys are skipping that part.
And tissue banks are regulated,
So more likely the thieves are
working with the Funeral Home.
They provide the
bodies to tissue banks.
I put together a list of
Funeral Homes in the area.
We can start with that. Great, yeah.
Hey, Rigsby, my boss
asked me to come,
You know, since I've worked
with CBI before. Hmm.
I'm not trying to get in
your face is all I'm saying.
Didn't think you were.
Okay, good. Okay.
Dr. Steiner, I presume.
What brings you back?
Good news, actually.
A small amount of blood was recovered
From the dirt under the
body at the crime scene.
It contains two distinct
DNA signatures.
The killer got cut, too.
Yes, probably while using
a knife on the victim.
There's not enough blood for an I.D.,
But there could be more on the corpse.
Interesting. Why did you come
and tell me that in person
Instead of calling?
I would like to assist in some
small way, if that's all right.
Okay. Let's go get
you a gun, shall we?
Kidding. Welcome. Come on.
Look sharp, Lisbon.
We have a visitor.
Dr. Steiner? Can I help you?
Well, actually, I...
Steiner's gonna be
joining us for a while.
Um... okay.
What is all this mess? It's Hartley's
calendar and phone records.
We're making a list of people
he saw before he died.
Meh. Clerical work.
We need to figure out what
the big secret is. What big secret?
Yeah, what big secret?
The big, weird secret that
the widow and the partner
And everyone won't tell us about
Because it's too shameful to mention.
It's funny you should mention that.
He... he did have an appointment
every week with no description.
Thursdays, 2:15 to 3:30.
No name, no address. Interesting.
Clerical work, huh? Touch?
If I may, his car's GPS
might have an address.
Yes, it might.
See? Useful already.
2729 Hillview Avenue.
This is the address
in Hartley's GPS.
Okay, what's the game with Steiner?
No game. What's he doing here, then?
What are any of us doing here?
We don't bring guests
on investigations.
Maybe we should. A different
mystery sleuth for each case.
Well, if this is some
gag you're pulling...
It's not. He asked
if he could come along,
And I said he could.
All right? That's it.
We're building bridges,
mending fences... okay.
Planting seeds... uh-huh.
Laying foundations. Okay.
It's a medical building, G.P.'s,
dentists, but mostly shrinks
How do you know who to talk to?
Any calls from his phone
records to this address?
No, but we can check his
bank records for payments.
Oh, we'd need a warrant for that.
I'd rather just
start knocking on doors.
Then we're gonna
need more people.
You'll have to clear that with admin.
Okay, everybody, outside! Outside!
Come on! It's not a drill! Whoo!
Oh, God, Jane.
Why do you do things like this?
Hustle it out. Hustle it out.
That's the way. Okay, come on.
All of you.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
My name is Patrick Jane.
I'm with the CBI.
We are looking for the doctor
who treated Timothy Hartley.
I know you have a doctor/patient
confidentiality thing.
Let's not worry about that right now.
Would Timothy Hartley's doctor
please raise his or her hand?
Raise it on up.
I know it's one of you.
Maybe to your right,
Maybe to your left. Up, up, up,
up with your hand. Bring it up.
Okay, so no one has raised their hand.
That doesn't matter because
I know that you, ma'am,
Are the person who we seek.
Please come forward.
Everyone else, thank you,
and back to your quackery.
What's your name, ma'am?
Dr. Wendelyne McCormick.
And I won't discuss my patients
Of the fact that
someone is my patient.
We're investigating the
murder of Timothy Hartley.
He was killed last night.
Oh, god.
All right.
How did you know it was me?
Everyone else was looking
around to see who it was,
But you weren't, because you knew.
Great. The fire department.
I'll go talk to 'em.
Tim had been in therapy
for about four months.
He'd had a traumatizing experience
That he wanted to work through.
What kind of an experience?
Agent, can I get some assurance
of discretion from you?
It's a sensitive matter
to the people around him.
We can't promise anything.
Very well.
About five months ago,
He had an abduction experience.
Excuse me?
He believed he was abducted
by extraterrestrial beings...
Taken to their ship, examined,
And released.
Kidnapped by aliens.
Cool.
I was being lifted by
the light, up and away.
I-I couldn't... couldn't do anything.
I was just being...
taken right to the ship.
It happened when
Hartley was driving home
From a trip to Reno.
We found a couple of these
videos on his personal laptop,
Some kind of diary of the event.
And once on the ship, there were...
There were beings all around me,
Small...
Just ash gray.
And there were a
little taller ones too...
They're the same color.
They were leaders, I think.
It just all feels so...
It feels so concrete,
So real.
Crazy. He sounds sincere to me.
Sincerely cuckoo.
I don't see any sign he's lying.
It could be a dream
that he experienced
During a hypnagogic state.
That would make it true for him,
But not objectively real. Exactly.
I agree with him completely.
Thousands of people say
it's happened to them.
They can't all be crazy or lying. Hmm.
I'm just saying you
should keep an open mind.
You can't prove there aren't aliens.
That's true. Okay, the point is,
the wife had to have known about this.
We need to talk to her again. Yeah.
Where are we with the body hunt?
We've identified eight funeral parlors
That had extensive legitimate
dealings with tissue banks.
We're gonna start with them.
We're splitting the interviews
with O'Laughlin.
All right, let me know what you find.
Okay. Watch the skies, Grace.
Tim told me as soon as it happened.
He said he met them in a
field outside Auburn.
Where we found his body? Mm-hmm.
He kept going back.
He couldn't tell me why.
I mean, he knew it wasn't rational.
Why didn't you tell us this before?
I got a call from Art Vella,
Tim's partner.
He told me not to
mention it, begged me.
He said it would be
devastating for the business.
You believed your husband's
story, didn't you?
That's why you were so scared
when the body disappeared.
Okay, okay.
Listen to me.
My husband wasn't crazy.
Okay?
He wouldn't lie to me about
something like that.
Rubbish! When someone tells you
something contrary to fact,
They are lying, full stop.
Don't start, mother.
Agents, my son-in-law was
drunk or drug-addled or both.
As for this tabloid trash
about men from Mars...
Ladies. How can you say that?
Ridiculous. Just ridiculous!
This is so like you, mother...
I've never heard
such twaddle in my life...
so closed off and close-minded.
And he said it with a straight face.
You honestly think...
Ladies. Ladies, that's enough.
Wait. What are you looking for?
Ah, yes.
You're a scotch man, right?
Uh, yes. I...
Oh, no, no. I-I shouldn't.
You really should.
Cheers.
You know, don't you?
Excuse me?
You know that I'm sick.
Why would Patrick Jane, of all people,
Invite me to a fancy house
And put a first-rate scotch
in my hand if he didn't know?
You've lost some weight... 8 pounds.
Yes.
Your face is looking drawn.
You're taking some
powerful medication.
I can see it in the
pallor of your skin.
Yes.
I'm dying.
I have a month...
Most likely, maybe less.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for the distraction.
Well, it's always good to...
Keep busy.
There's probably some, uh,
Havana cigars in that box there.
No. No, no. I...
I couldn't.
Could I?
Well, you're right.
This is a good cigar.
The only other time
That I had been in a room like this
Was to examine a man
who died accidentally
In the middle of an autoerotic ritual.
Well, I bet he died with
a smile on his face.
Excuse me.
Can I help you? Ahem.
Why did you tell Peregrine
Hartley to lie to us, sir?
I didn't tell her to lie.
I asked Peregrine not to raise
certain relevant information.
Why'd you do that?
Tim was the brain.
I handled clients, administration.
It's all about confidence.
If the investors hear about
alien probes and whatnot,
Confidence goes right out the window.
Then I assume you asked him not
to talk about this. Constantly.
But Mr. Hartley
was growing certain
His experiences were real.
He must've wanted to talk about it.
We had some arguments about it.
Bad arguments?
I didn't kill tim because he wanted
To go public with his cuckoo story.
You need to talk to that UFO
fruitcake that Tim met.
They're friends about a week,
And then tim wanted nothing
more to do with him.
I think he was trying to
squeeze some money out of Tim.
What's his name?
Kirk. Can you believe that?
Newsom Kirk.
Is there any way
you can keep this quiet?
I doubt it.
$2.8 billion in assets.
We're going down because
my partner thought he was
kidnapped by little green men.
Gray.
What?
The little men. They're gray.
Thanks for your time. Appreciate it.
Two down, two to go.
Wanna grab some food?
Oh, there's an errand I wanna run.
Give me half an hour. I'll catch up.
Where you going? I'll take you.
You don't need to do that.
Oh, come on. How far is it?
It's a little ways. It's okay.
It's a wedding thing. Oh, I see.
Why don't I drop you off?
I'll grab something to eat,
And then stay in the car, okay?
Sure.
Hello.
O'Laughlin. I tried Grace.
She didn't answer.
She's busy.
I've got something.
Gary Wineman, funeral director.
Mentioned tissue banks,
and he got very nervous.
Mr. Wineman, these are
my colleagues from CBI,
Agents Rigsby and Van Pelt.
Did agent O'Laughlin mention
what this was about, sir?
Uh, some... bodies have been stolen
That might have gone to a tissue bank?
No, that's the FBI's investigation.
We're investigating a murder.
Oh.
You didn't say anything about that.
I certainly don't know anything about it.
Well, I hope so, sir.
A case like this,
anyone connected to it...
Even remotely connected...
is in big trouble.
Best thing to protect yourself...
Be very clear about what you
know and what you've done.
Oh, god. Uh, look...
W-we...
My wife had a baby girl,
And we needed a little extra cash,
So I started selling
bodies to tissue banks...
A-all... all legitimate.
I got permission every time.
But the banks always want more bodies,
And my wife got pregnant again.
Look, who came to you?
My cousin. Not a good person.
He said that if we split the fee,
He could provide bodies,
no permission necessary.
All I have to do was
dummy up paperwork,
Giving them false names.
Did he bring you a corpse today?
No, no, no, no.
But I... he has done this before
With other funeral homes.
His name is Owen Melling.
I-I-I had no I...
where is he now, sir?
Melling's done time for
assault, armed robbery,
And truck hijacking.
Did the truck jobs with a
buddy named Jim Matthews.
Both are on parole.
Melling owes 15 years, Matthews... 12.
And they know if they get picked up,
They're violated back in.
It's good times.
Owen Melling?
CBI.
We need to talk to you about
a robbery this morning.
Just wanna get some facts straight.
Come down to the office,
and we can explain.
Jim. Cops.
Jim Matthews?
Yeah. What's up?
Says it's about some
robbery this morning.
So what?
We were right here. That's right.
Been here all day.
Yeah, well, we still
need to talk to you.
Now get your hands
out of your pocket.
Hands where we can see 'em.
You heard him. Now.
Don't hassle my boy!
He ain't done nothin'!
Put the weapon down, ma'am.
You just wanna make more
trouble for him. I won't have it.
We just wanna talk to your son.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Just put down the gun, ma'am.
Gun!
O'Llaughlin, Grace is in trouble.
Cover me.
O'Laughlin!
Grace, get down!
On the ground! Face down! Now!
Get on the ground!
How'd the interview
with Matthews go?
Didn't.
He asked for a lawyer.
What'd you find in Melling's house?
No sign of Hartley's body.
Forensics is checking
the pickup for DNA.
I got something.
According to his cell phone records,
Melling made a call yesterday
to a Wellview Funeral Home.
Could be where they
dropped off Hartley's body.
Get Steiner and go and check it out.
If the body's there,
He's the one to I.D. It.
Sure.
Tracked down an address
for Newsom Kirk,
the guy Hartley had
a falling-out with.
He runs an organization for abductees
Called the Fourth Kind Foundation.
Office is downtown.
Does he have a sheet?
Running it now.
We'll go talk to him.
Call if anything pops. Okay.
Newsom Kirk, I'm agent Lisbon.
This is agent Cho.
We're with the CBI.
Yes, yes. You called. Welcome.
Welcome.
Agent Cho, you... you've...
you've been, haven't you?
Excuse me?
Up. Taken, with them.
No.
Well, I'm getting a... I'm
getting a definite sense.
It sometimes takes a person years
To realize they've had the experience.
Timothy Hartley.
Of course. Sorry.
You met him through
the foundation, right?
Yeah. We're here to serve abductees,
Um, help them come to terms
with their experience.
Oh. Spread the word.
Uh, Tim wanted to talk about
what he'd been going through.
He asked us to keep it in
confidence, and... and we did.
And that's all you did...
talk about his experience?
No. As a matter of fact,
Tim had a lot of money.
And frankly, we... we need money,
We had... we had several
quite serious discussions
About funding this... this place.
As a child...
Did... did you have, um, dreams
Where you were floating
through the house
As though pulled by an unseen force?
No.
Uh, we heard that the, uh, two of you
Had some sort of a falling-out?
He decided that he wanted to
start his own foundation.
Uh, his right, I say.
It never got angry?
No, no. Uh, if you're looking
For someone Tim
had a fight with,
You should talk to that shrink of his.
Uh, McCormick.
She wanted to write a book about him.
He said no. She was angry.
Okay. Boss, from Rigsby.
Uh, Mr. Newsom, is your
real name Garrett Rosten?
And did you spend a year
in Chino prison for fraud?
Because your arrest
record says you did.
In my previous life, I
was Garrett Rosten, yes.
Mr. Hartley seems like the kind of guy
Who would research somebody
If he was considering funding them.
Did he find out about this?
I never hid Garrett.
I'm simply a different person now.
Not that different.
There's a bench warrant out for
your arrest for kiting checks.
We're gonna have to take you in.
Turn around, please.
It's... it's okay. It's...
Just a misunderstanding.
Hey, agent.
The important thing is that you
take a look inside yourself
And start questioning
those experiences...
That you can't explain.
Never happened.
I believe you.
Wake up.
Newsom Kirk posted bail.
He's gonna be gone in an hour.
Just in time for the
6:10 to Alpha Centauri.
He was right about
Hartley's psychiatrist.
She did propose a book,
but she withdrew it.
So she had motive. Kinda.
Who do you think did it?
Jabba the Hutt.
Seriously. Ming the merciless.
Okay. Alf?
When the aliens do come,
I hope they eat you. Mm.
Lisbon.
Theresa, Brenda Shettrick.
A local news crew is about
to interview Dr. Steiner
About the Hartley case.
Just thought you'd like to know.
He's supposed to be looking
for Hartley's body.
No, he's here.
What interview?
Some background on tissue
banks and the corpse trade.
There's a lot of interest.
He offered to do it.
You didn't know anything?
I'll be right there.
Bye, Lisbon. Oh.
The legitimate trade in
tissue is a valuable source
Of biological material
for medical use.
Unfortunately, this illegal trade
Has halted the investigation
Into the death of Timothy Hartley.
How's that?
Well, I-I just came
from a funeral home
Where we had hoped to find mr.
Hartley's body,
And it's... it's... it's not there.
The thieves have hidden it somewhere.
And there is crucial
evidence... blood evidence...
On Mr. Hartley's body that
will identify the killers.
Brenda.
If we don't find that evidence...
Now. Guys, that's it.
Thanks very much.
Did I do something wrong?
We don't talk to the
press about evidence.
It kinda tells the killer
what we're looking for.
Oh. Sorry.
How did I do otherwise?
Oh, good.
Hey, Cho.
Yeah.
I think O'Laughlin flaked
on Van Pelt yesterday.
What do you mean?
Well, he saw she was in trouble
and he didn't do anything.
Guess he was scared. It happens.
Yeah. Van Pelt doesn't know this?
No.
I don't know.
The question is,
does she need to know?
Yeah, it's tough.
Your call.
You saw the news story
on Hartley's body?
Well, I lied. I did find the body.
There is evidence on it,
And it will convict you of murder.
But I haven't given
the police the body.
I've kept it, and
I'm willing to sell it,
Along with my silence, for $50,000.
Because I'm a dying man.
All I want is a few days of
real comfort before I'm gone.
Think about it.
You know how to reach me.
How was that?
Not bad.
Little over-the-top,
But, you know, credible, nonetheless.
Sorry.
Still getting used
to all this deception.
What deception?
You did find Hartley's
body at a funeral home.
Yes, but there was no
blood evidence on it.
You can't catch a fish without bait.
We will tell agent Lisbon
what's going on, yes?
Oh, yeah, eventually.
Agent Lisbon's a good person.
She reminds me of...
Never mind.
Showtime. Huh?
Let's go.
Whoo! Whoo!
Yes?
Testing one, two.
Testing two.
Yes, Dr. Steiner, We can
hear you, just like before.
I'm a little nervous.
You're doing a great job.
You look the part.
Are you sure about this?
Are you ever gonna tire
of asking me that? No.
Someone's coming.
Go.
Dr. Steiner?
Put your hands where I can see 'em!
Hands! Hands in the air!
I'm not armed.
I'm... I'm not armed.
It's the butler! It's the butler!
It's the butler!
It's the but... the butler did it!
I always wanted to say that.
But wait. It gets better.
Ms. Cook.
Good evening. Remember me?
I can't hear anything with this.
The good doctor here told us
that Timothy Hartley's murder
cut himself whilst doing the killing.
Yeah. Would you mind terribly
showing me your hand?
Oh.
You must let Harrison go.
He has done nothing but serve
me faithfully and well.
As I explained, ma'am,
Our D.A. Will drop the
charges against your Butler,
If you answer our questions honestly.
I feel like I'm haggling in a
bazaar over the cost of a rug.
But if you will release
Harrison, then I will speak.
Your son-in-law was about to go public
With the whole alien adventure
thing, wasn't he? More than that.
He wanted to start a global
foundation for abductees,
To see to their needs and
promote their cause.
He was gonna call it The
Cook Family Foundation.
Well, that wasn't going to happen.
No, you cannot do this.
I won't allow it.
It's not something you can stop.
Try me. I am not without
resources, young man.
But he said he was going to
use his own money for it.
And then he said...
time's on my side, Elspeth.
What do you mean, Timothy?!
Timothy, come back here!
I knew what he meant.
Hartley was going to wait
Until I was dead,
and then use my money
And my daughter to
turn the Cook name
Into an international joke.
So the next time he went to that
place he was always visiting,
We followed.
Why slit Hartley's throat?
That was the telltale sign...
A hunter's humanity, if you will.
You learned how to hunt
and kill at a young age,
Didn't you, Elspeth?
Your father taught you.
Yes. He was very firm on that point.
"Never let the animal suffer."
I got awfully cross with
Consuela for mislaying this.
I shall have to apologize.
Mm.
Hey. What's up?
There's something I have to
talk to you about. What's that?
Wayne?
What is it?
A friend of mine is a ranger
at Vandermeer State Park,
And maybe I can get him to give
you a waiver to get married
At that quaker meeting house.
Really?
Yeah. I think. I can try.
Wayne, that's fantastic. Mwah.
Thank you so much. Yeah.
I'm gonna call Craig.
Yeah, okay.
Please.
Thank you for coming by.
Oh, it's no problem.
Nice place. Tidy.
Thank you.
Please.
I wanted to tell you
how much I appreciated
Your letting me come along
on your investigation.
It was fun.
Hmm, it was fun, wasn't it?
That was my pleasure.
Thank you.
Um, look... ahh.
Won't beat around the bush.
About me dying,
I-I know what's going to happen now.
I've seen it.
There are no mysteries.
It's going to get bad...
Very soon,
And then worse.
And I have no interest
In letting nature take its course.
You understand?
Uh, yes.
You, uh, you want to kill yourself.
In a nutshell.
I have pills I can take.
The problem is,
If there is an unexplained death,
If a body is found in an apartment,
There is an investigation, an autopsy.
Mm.
And the idea of being examined,
Of being a body on the...
On the table...
But if the death is witnessed
by a law enforcement officer,
No investigation is required.
I'm not a law enforcement officer.
You're close enough, I think.
I don't know that I can do
it, that I can witness that.
I'm not even sure that killing
yourself is the best idea.
It's what I'm going to do.
Well, that's your choice.
But, uh...
I understand. I...
I'm sorry.
This was a t...
Terrible imposition.
I-I shouldn't have.
Please.
Forget I said anything.
I'm sorry.
Do you have any tea?
Yes, I do.
I could really use a cup of tea.
Okay.
Sure.
Uh...
There's cookies in the cupboard. Yeah.
Uh... uh, would you like a cup?
Thank you. Yeah.
Well, uh, I'm going in
the other room now.
I'll be a few minutes.
Yeah. Take your time.
Here.
Mmm.
The note in the
dead man's... pocket...
You... you had an arrangement
With the deputy, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
I knew it.
Yeah.
It's an old carny magic trick.
You did magic?
Oh, yeah.
I first started out,
uh, working close-up
With, uh, cards and coins.
Really?
Yeah. I'll show you.
Got a coin in here.
Yeah. Okay.
See that coin?
It's there, right?
And it's gone.
It's there...
Then it's gone.
Amazing.
It's really quite simple.
It's there...
And then it's gone.
Patrick...
Thank you.
Just watch the coin.
And it's gone.
It's there...
And then it's gone.
Sync by YYeTs
Corrected by ThreeSixes
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net